<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Manchester United</string>
    <string name="goalkeeper">GoalKeeper</string>
    <string name="defender">Defender</string>
    <string name="midfielder">Midfielder</string>
    <string name="attacker">Attacker</string>
    
    <string name="van_der_sar">Manchester United went through a whole lot of trouble trying to find a suitable replacement for the "Great Dane," Peter Schmeichel. 

Manchester United experimented with a lot of high profile goal keepers including Mark Bosnich, Massimo Taibi, Fabien Barthez, Tim Howard and Roy Carroll, before finally landing the Dutchman. 

Van der Sar joined United on 10 June 2005 for a paltry sum of £2 million, which is astonishing considering how much they forked out for David de Gea. 

Perhaps his most memorable moment is the penalty save against Nicholas Anelka to give Manchester United the Champions League; his nickname was aptly changed to "Van der Save."

On 27 January 2009, he also set the record for the number of consecutive clean sheets at 11 games and also broke the record for going the longest without conceding a goal at 1,311 minutes. 

Stats aside, the Dutchman exuded class through and through, and he deserved to be No.1 in the list of greatest goalkeepers of Manchester United.</string>


    <string name="peter_schmeichel">He would have been No. 1 only if he hadnt made the cardinal sin of joining Manchester City.

Schmeichel deserves plaudits for overseeing perhaps the most successful era of Manchester United.

An ever intimidating presence in the United goal, at 6 ft 4 in, Peter Schmeichel was the keystone that allowed Manchester United to top the league again in the 1990s.

In the 1999 FA-Cup final, he also saved Dennis Bergkamps penalty kick in the dying moments to send the game into extra time.

Furthermore, in Roy Keanes absence, he captained the side to a memorable victory in the 1999 Champions League final over Bayern Munich, thereby completing a historic treble.

He also holds the record number of clean sheets, with 42 percent of his games having been clean sheets.</string>


    <string name="david_de_gea">David De Gea made history in May 2016 by becoming the first Manchester United player to win three consecutive Sir Matt Busby Player of the Year awards. It was an unprecedented honour for the goalkeeper and it cemented his status as a fan-favourite at Old Trafford.

The Reds’ no.1 signed a four-year contract at the beginning of 2015/16, with an option for a further year, following a summer of intense speculation regarding Real Madrids well-documented pursuit of his signature. Finishing fifth in the Barclays Premier League was a disappointment for De Gea and the team, but success was experienced by lifting the FA Cup and a first trophy for the club since 2013.

De Geas road to Old Trafford began at Atletico Madrid’s academy. Tall, athletic and confident with the ball, he progressed quickly through the youth ranks and spent his first professional season, 2008/09, with the club’s reserves. A first-team debut arrived early in the following term via a substitute appearance against FC Porto in the UEFA Champions League on 30 September 2009 - and thereafter he never looked back.

De Gea capped his maiden campaign in Atletico Madrids first team by playing a major role in winning the UEFA Europa League - the clubs first major European trophy in almost 50 years. His already</string>


    <string name="alex_stepney">Alex Stepney joined Manchester United from Chelsea for a then record fee of £55,000, having made just one appearance for the Chelsea outfit.

He went on to make more appearances in goal for United than any other keeper with 539 appearances.

Mancheser United won the League in 1967, thereby allowing them to enter the European Cup the following season.

With Stepney in goal, Manchester United won the European Cup against Benfica. A memorable incident form the game is when Benfica striker Eusebio drew out an astonishing save from Stepney during the dying moments of the game, which caused Eusebio to stand and applaud the Englishman.</string>


    <string name="jimmy_rimmer">Alex Stepney was a solid keeper, but many believe that his under-study, Jimmy Rimmer was an even better keeper.

He spent 11 years at Old Trafford, deputizing for Stepney.

However, he left for Arsenal where he was the undisputed keeper for three years and then transferred to Aston Villa.

At Aston Villa, he was the premier goal keeper for six years.

The highlight at Villa was when he he guided them to a UEFA Champions League victory in 1982 over Bayern Munich.</string>


    <string name="harry_gregg">Harry Gregg, often called the "Hero of Munich" because he pulled some of his teammates from the burning plane during the Munich air disaster including Bobby Charlton, Jackie Blanchflower, Dennis Violett and also Sir Matt Busby, was also a prodigious goalkeeping talent.

He was voted the best goalkeeper at the 1958 World Cup, and outshone his closest competitor Lev Yashin by 478 votes to 122 votes.

Although he did not have any medals to his name whilst playing for Manchester United, as a serious shoulder injury kept him out of the 1963 FA Cup victory and a series of injuries meant he played fewer games than required to earn a medal during Uniteds league victory in 1964-65 and 1966-67, he is widely regarded as one of the best goalkeepers ever to have donned the United jersey.</string>


    <string name="reg_allen">Wildly considered one of the best goalkeepers in the world, Reg Allen transferred to Manchester United on 6 June 1950 for £11,000, a then world-record fee, from Queens Park Rangers.

He was widely heralded as one of the best goalkeepers of his era.

However, he is a bit lower in the ranking, as he only played in the side for two years and his role was usurped by Jack Crompton and eventually Ray Wood.</string>


    <string name="steve_bruce">You had to love the guy. He was fearless, both as a defender and an attacker. He joined the Gills in 1979 and, after more than 200 games, moved on to Norwich City and finally Manchester United where, in 1987, he became one of Sir Alexs early signings.

No United fan will ever forget the goal above and especially Fergies reaction. Bruce went on to play nine seasons, with 414 appearances and 51 goals before leaving for Birmingham City at 35.

In the 1990/91 season alone, he scored 19 goals in just 50 matches! Many strikers would be delighted at that return.

They say that centre-backs are like London buses. You wait ages for a good one, and then two come along at the same time.

Maybe the truth is that two players forge a partnership, where their mutual understanding is much of what makes them great. That was surely the case with Steve and our next choice, because despite his greatness for Manchester United, Bruce never got a full cap for England.

This next chap did, despite possibly being the lesser of the two.</string>


    <string name="gary_neville">If there was ever any doubt—which there wasnt—this is all Gary needed to make himself a United legend.

There can equally be no doubt that he is the greatest right-back United ever produced.

Is he our greatest full-back? Tony Dunne and Denis Irwin would have something to say about that, but probably.

Gary is far from the most skillful full-back you would ever see. Yes, he was an attacking full-back, but not like Roberto Carlos, because first and foremost Gary was a gritty, uncompromising defender. He is in the same school as Brucey and Nemanja in having the capability to have fitted well 30, 50 or even 100 years ago.

He is arguably the most combative defender United ever had.

He made himself capable of attacking at an international standard, primarily in his overlapping partnership with David Beckham, for United and England.

His goal-scoring feats wont be remembered in 50 years, with only seven in 602 appearances, but that made some more memorable.

This video sums up everything Gary was to United. Who knows, one day he may return as manager...</string>


    <string name="rio_ferdinand">Can you believe that Rios middle name is Gavin? He began his career with West Ham United and, lest we forget, also played for Leeds United, including being their captain, before Sir Alex signed him for £30 million.

As a lad, Rio played at centre forward, but by the time he was 18, he was already good enough to be called up as Englands youngest defender ever.

Many of us who watched him progress as a young defender saw the greatness of Franz Beckenbauer, but sadly the sweeper role has hardly ever caught on in England.

Ferdinand has until recently had the pace and footballing skill to be an attacking centre-back, much in the mould of Mats Hummels of Dortmund.

Clearly he is under instructions from the manager, because if he had the freedom to roam, he is skillful enough to have scored a lot more goals.

We must hope that he too is fully fit for the new season, now that his back troubles are behind him (oops!).

When he joined almost exactly 10 years ago, to replace Jaap Stam, he was the most expensive footballer in British history and the most expensive defender in the world for the second time (previously when he joined Leeds).

He has been fairly compared to the greats of Italian football, Alessandro Nesta and Paolo Maldini, and would surely have become a legend in Serie A.

If he ever wants a swansong away from Old Trafford, thats where he should head.

With 398 appearances so far, he will surely grace that United top 21 before he hangs up his boots to become an Old Trafford youth team coach and club Ambassador.

If there is one tiny criticism, he should have scored more than his seven goals to date.</string>


    <string name="nemanja_vidic">This is what weve missed.

I can recall almost 60 years of football and watched the great Bill Foulkes play both for England and United.

But Nemanja Vidic is the greatest centre-back and defender we have ever had.

He is a throw-back to the old days of blood and thunder, when full-backs kicked wingers up in the air and centre halves flattened the opposition centre forward.

The difference is that you now have to do it legally...

Again, you cannot consider Vidic without his world-class partner Rio Ferdinand. Like Bruce and Pallister, they also have had an uncanny understanding.

In truth, Vidic could do with more pace, as Fernando Torres has proved on more than one occasion, but his timing and execution more than make up for that. Lets hope he returns fully fit from his knee ligament injury.

With Ferdinand having a renaissance now that his back is better and he has accepted his own limitations, even 30 times next season would be enough for this partnership to bring trophies back to Old Trafford once again.

So far Nemanja has 243 appearances for United with 18 goals. Weve missed him, and now that he has retired from international duty, lets hope we can get at least three more years at the top out of him.</string>


    <string name="denis_irwin">Denis Irwin is undoubtedly Uniteds best left-back ever. If he had been in the team last season, we would have walked the Premier League.

He is also one of Uniteds most consistently under-rated players. He is humble and a very nice man, who has never crowed of his achievements. He was also a more-than-useful right-back, which prompted Gary Neville to include him in his best 11 in that position, just to fit him in.

He was one of the most consummate penalty takers ever, also.

Like Eric Cantona, we could also forgive him for having played for Leeds United.

Denis moved to Old Trafford in 1990, a "steal" at £625,000 when you consider what he went on to achieve.

In 529 appearances, he scored 33 goals, many of them penalties. He won 19 major trophies, including seven Premier League titles and of course the Champions League.

There would be a case for him to be the best Premiership left-back of all time, even ahead of Ashley Cole.</string>

    <string name="jaap_stam">Oh dear, oh dear...

How many times would Jaap Stam have played for United if he hadnt written his book and suffered an Achilles heel injury?

Sir Alex has readily admitted that selling Stam, even for £16.5 million at age 29, was a big mistake. He was honest enough to include Stam in his greatest-ever United XI.

Stam only made 121 appearances during which he won six trophies, including of course a Champions League medal.

He went on to make a further 143 appearances for Lazio, Milan and Ajax. How much more could United have achieved if he had finished his career at Old Trafford, including playing alongside Rio Ferdinand before Vidic arrived?</string>


    <string name="patrice_evra">Hates Luise Suarez</string>


    <string name="bill_foulkes">Four players epitomised the Busby Babes.

Duncan Edwards is enshrined as a legend, despite being killed at the age of 21. He remains the finest footballer I have ever seen in 63 years.

Sir Bobby Charlton shares that opinion. The Red Knight went on to become one of Uniteds three greatest players of all time.

But there were two reluctant heroes who, like Charlton, kept the red flag flying in the disastrous aftermath.

One was Harry Gregg, who is one of Uniteds greatest goalkeepers. More important, he has ever since been feted as the hero of Munich, having saved the lives of his friends, putting his own life at risk unthinkingly. He has never sought reward or attention but was given a testimonial this year in recognition.

The other was Bill Foulkes.

If he were playing in 2012, Bill would be a legend, compared to Vidic or Stam. He was also a reluctant hero. He felt guilty to have survived the crash, like Charlton. Like Sir Bobby he had to be pressed into action again and, in Foulkes case as captain.

Around these two players, Jimmy Murphy at first and then Sir Matt Busby when he recovered, began to rebuild the shattered team. Without these men, Manchester United may not have become the force they are today.

Bill Foulkes captained United in the Munich aftermath and eventually got his reward in their European Cup win, having scored the goal against Real Madrid that took them to the Final.

In all, he made 608 appearances for United with nine goals and stands fourth on the all-time list, behind only Sir Bobby, Paul Scholes and Ryan Giggs.</string>


    <string name="paul_mcgrath">You cannot define greatness simply by statistics.

When we are very old, we can look at the record books and see that Paul McGrath made only 163 appearances for United.

But like Jaap Stam, Sir Alex would readily tell you that Paul was one of the greatest.

It is well documented that Paul had personal challenges.

That he played for Ireland 83 times was in itself a miracle, although if he had been the fully fit athlete that Maldini was, who knows what his achievements would have been.

Like Ferdinand, McGrath would not have been out of place in Italy. He also had the ability to move at great pace while appearing to lope along.

When Sir Alex decided he must break the drinking culture at Old Trafford, legends McGrath and Whiteside were the most high-profile casualties.

At first United were considering retiring McGrath with a testimonial, but their former manager, Ron Atkinson, eventually bought him for £400,000.

McGrath made a further 252 appearances for Villa and won the PFA Player of the Year award, so much was he endeared to his fellow professionals.

He was converted to a defender while at United and, but for his alcohol problems, may have finished his career there.</string>


    <string name="phil_neville"> </string>


    <string name="paul_scholes">Paul Scholes won 10 Premier League titles with United and has played his entire youth and professional career with the club.

He has so far made 683 appearances over 19 seasons, scoring 151 goals.

United discovered how important the central midfielder was to the team after he retired and left a giant gap in the center of the park.

Sir Alex Ferguson convinced Scholes to come out of retirement and the Englishman has been extremely effective since his return.

He is one of the most complete midfielders in team history. His speed, skill and vision have made him dangerous going forward, while his work-rate and aggressive style have allowed him to be a fearsome defender.

His loyalty to the club, in addition to his magnificent talent, make him the second best midfield player ever to take to the pitch for United.</string>


    <string name="george_best">Maradona—good. Pelé—better. George—as his name suggests—best.

Only a man with the last name "Best" could top all Manchester United midfielders.

The Northern Irish national scored 179 goals in 470 appearances across 11 seasons with the club.

He was an indomitable talent who could beat players with speed or skill and finish with both feet.

Best made his debut with the first team at age 17 and won the league championship twice. He was also an instrumental part of the 1968 European Cup winning team.

In the same season, his unstoppable attacking ability earned him 32 goals and the Ballon dOr award for best European player.

Unfortunately, he played as hard off the field as he did on it, and was an alcoholic with an extravagant lifestyle.

Bests career with United could have lasted longer—he stopped playing for the club at age 27.

However, his stint with Red Devils was so unforgettable that it has earned him his rightful place atop all other Manchester midfielders.</string>


    <string name="ryan_giggs">Ryan Giggs 899 appearances for Manchester United is a club record, making the Welshman the iron man of the Premiership.

At 38-years-old, Giggs—in his 22nd season at Old Trafford—still plays regularly for the Red Devils and is looking to add to his tally of 162 goals.

The winger was more often than not the fastest player on the field during the early stages of his career and he used his pace to terrorize opposing defenses.

As he grew older, he reformed his style of play to adapt to his fading athleticism and showed the could be effective as a central midfielder.

Giggs grew up in the United youth program and was called up to the first team in 1991. Since his debut with the first team, he has won the EPL an incredible 12 times.

His speed when he was younger, and his veteran savvy as he grew older, make Giggs one of the three best midfielders in club history.</string>


    <string name="roy_keane">Roy Keane earned the nickname "Captain Fantastic" for his many years of service as the Manchester United skipper.

The Irishman brought an edge to midfield and never allowed United to be intimidated by the opposition. He was also an extraordinarily smart and skilled player, and scored 51 goals in 480 appearances with the club.

His best moment at United came in the 1998-99 Champions League semifinal against Juventus. Losing 2-0 early in the game, Keane scored an incredible goal off of a corner kick to spark a memorable comeback.

His heroic effort was even more remarkable because he had already accumulated enough yellow cards to receive a suspension for the final. Despite knowing he would miss the next game, Keane refused to quit and led United to a 3-2 victory. His performance prompted this quote from his manager Sir Alex Ferguson:

"It was the most emphatic display of selflessness I have seen on a football field. Pounding over every blade of grass, competing if he would rather die of exhaustion than lose, he inspired all around him. I felt it was an honour to be associated with such a player."

Keane was a true leader during his 13 year career with the club and won seven Premier League medals. His grit and his grace made him one of the true legends of United history.</string>


    <string name="david_beckham">Before he married Posh Spice and became a tabloid fixture, David Beckham was just a soccer player—and a damn good one too.

Beckham rose to superstardom with Manchester United by scoring 85 goals in 394 appearances.

The highlight of his 13 year career at Old Trafford came in 1999 when he helped the team win the FA Cup, Champions League and Premier League.

The midfielders crosses and free kicks—not to mention his underrated speed and dribbling skills— helped United win six league championships.

But Beckham, just like Ronaldo, moved on to Real Madrid when he still had productive years left in him. He ranks higher than the Portuguese star because he spent more years with the club, but could have been higher on the list had he chosen to stay in Manchester.</string>


    <string name="cristiano_ronaldo">Ronaldo had one of the best seasons ever for a United player in 2007-08, when he scored 42 goals and led his team to Premier League and Champions League titles.

The winger was selected FIFA World Player of the Year for his play that season.

During a stint which lasted from 2003 to 2009, Ronaldo scored 118 goals and made 292 appearances before leaving for Real Madrid in a deal worth £80 million.

It made him the most expensive player in club football history.

No player on the list had a better season than Ronaldos 2007-08 gem, but his decision to leave for Madrid and cut his United career short kept him from receiving a higher rank.</string>


    <string name="paul_pogba"></string>


    <string name="nobby_stiles">Norbert "Nobby" Stiles was another vital piece to Uniteds midfield in the 1960s, with his elite marking skills and tenacity.

The relentless defensive midfielder appeared for United 394 times and scored 19 goals between 1960 and 1971.

He often played beside Crerand and the two formed a menacing pair in the middle of the field.

The highlight of Stiles career with the Red Devils came when the team beat Benfica 4-1 in extra time to become the first English side to win the European Cup in 1968.

Stiles flourished after being given the difficult task of guarding Benficas legendary forward, Eusébio, who had won the European Golden Boot for most domestic league goals that year.

His defensive prowess places him one notch above his midfield partner on this list.</string>


    <string name="paddy_crerand">Crerand played for Manchester United from 1963 to1971 and helped the team to two league championships in 1964-65 and 1966-67.

Appearing in 397 games and scoring 15 goals, the Scotsman played primarily as a holding midfielder and was a stabilizing force for United.

By no means a flashy player, he was known more for his solid tackling and pinpoint passes, which helped create hundreds of goals for team mates Bobby Charlton, Dennis Law and George Best. </string>


    <string name="ole_gunnar_solskjaer"></string>

    <string name="bryan_robson">Bryan Robson was a prolific goal-scorer and playmaker during his 14 season career with Manchester United.

He was a jack-of-all-trades who had few weaknesses, and United kept him in the center of the field in order to keep him as close to the action as possible.

Robson scores 99 goals in 461 appearances while playing from 1981 to 1994.

Unfortunately, the bulk of the Englishmans career came during Uniteds 26 year title drought, but he was part of two well-deserved Premier League championships in his final couple of seasons with the club. </string>

    <string name="nani"></string>


    <string name="wayne_rooney"></string>


    <string name="denis_law">The original King of the Stretford End, Law was deadly in front of goal. One third of the Holy Trinity along with George Best and Bobby Charlton, the Scot weighed in with 237 goals in 398 starts between 1962 and 1973.

He was voted European Footballer of the Year in 1964, and was desperately unlucky not to have been at Wembley when United lifted the European Cup in 68—he was in hospital having a knee operation.

Nevertheless, his feats on the pitch for United make him worthy number two in our list</string>


    <string name="eric_cantona">The mercurial Frenchmans séjour in Manchester was a whirlwind from start to finish. The catalyst for Uniteds era-beginning title triumph in 1993, Cantona went on to win four league titles and two FA Cups, scoring 82 times in 184 starts.

But it wasnt just goals that he brought to the club. His flair, panache and sheer arrogance left a lasting impression on a whole generation of youngsters at the club, who would go on to become world stars themselves.</string>


    <string name="bobby_charlton"></string>


    <string name="zlatan_ibrahimovic"></string>


    <string name="teddy_sheringham"></string>


    <string name="dwight_yorke"></string>


    <string name="dennis_viollet">Few strikers reach the magic 30 mark in one season, and even fewer do it in just 36 league games. Only one did it in a matter of months, after having survived the Munich air crash: Dennis Violet.

His 32 goals in the 1959-60 were a testament to his talent and to his determination, yet he never seemed to get the credit he deserved, and is considered one of the most underrated strikers of all time.</string>


    <string name="ruud_van_nistelroy">A goalscorer par excellence, Van Nistelrooy had a nose for goal like no other. His record speaks for itself: 150 goals in just 200 starts over five years at the club. During that time he managed to win the Premier League, the FA Cup, the League Cup and the Community Shield, and could usually be relied on to find the back of the net.

It was just a shame that he left the club for Real Madrid amid some acrimony.</string>


    <string name="mark_hughes">Hughes enjoyed two spells at United, but it during his second that he really had an impact. Most notably when, in the 1991 European Cup Winners Cup final against his former club Barcelona, he netted twice to propel United to glory.

He was a master of holding the ball up—largely thanks to the tree trunks that masqueraded as his thighs. Hughes was also fond of the spectacular, and few of the 163 goals he scored were tap-ins.</string>


    <string name="andy_cole">Cole had plenty of detractors during his time at United, many of whom unfairly accused him of being wasteful in front of goal. All strikers miss chances, but the truly great ones keep getting into goal scoring positions.

Cole fits the latter category, and his 121 goals from 231 starts prove just how prolific he was. His partnership with Dwight Yorke was, at times, a joy to behold and few United fans will ever forget his contribution during the Treble-winning season of 1999.</string>

</resources>

